If you want a big harvest.
null
So...
We'll see what it looks like tomorrow.
As usual, I graze with Frolic.
But only put out four cages this time.
So we'll see how it goes.
null
The reason for the grazing cages is that it will be a little more difficult
harder for the crayfish to access the bait
So they stay longer in the cages.
null
I only have four cages so it goes pretty fast.
I apparently had five cages.
null
Then I put a little loose in this and we will see if there is anything.
I can't go up and pick up a grazing cage.
Frolic "Fresh Ox" - Someone asked what kind I used.
null
Almost every time I post a movie about the pond or cancer cultivation
So is someone who hears and says "what ugly water you have".
null
I am fully aware of this, but do you have a pond with natural clay bottom without cloth